I wonder if you do have to acknowledge the barbarity,
the brutality of the attack on Israelis in southern Israel by Hamas
before this can move forwards.
Oh, God.
I mean, I can't believe I'm hearing the same thing over and over again.
This is a preoccupation with the Western media
because something happened to Israel for the first time in its history.
Everybody's up in arms and its victims have to condemn themselves.
Israel has been doing this to us for decades.
Peacemean, day in, day out.
People killed, almost demolished.
And we're telling you how many Palestinians have been killed
by a brutal Israeli occupation.
Total siege in Gaza, total destruction and blood theft in the West Bank.
Nobody brings Hamas spokespeople, Israeli spokespeople,
and say, do you condemn this?
Isn't this brutal?
Isn't this genocide?
Isn't this?
No.
But the moment people under siege, look at Gaza,
it's an area where people haven't had a day of nomad life.
And then when they lash out, when they break out,
immediately all sorts of horrific labels are used.
Were the Israeli citizens legitimate targets?
It's using, as I said, this logic, using this logic.
I just want to be clear, are you saying that the Israeli citizens were legitimate targets?
No, I don't believe in civilians being legitimate targets at all.
At all.
In the same way as we are not legitimate targets of Israel.
Our homes, our lands are not at its disposal.
Our freedom, our rights have been denied.
No, they don't put words in my mouth.
Never.
Civilians are never legitimate targets.
But what I'm talking about is the double standard.
Israel is an occupying power.
This has to be acknowledged.
Israel has been torturing the Palestinians since 1947.
It is time this stops.
It is time this to stop.
And here we go.
There are three things that are not legitimate targets of Israel.
And when you have to be diagnosed by Israel.
There are two things that are both broken.
The more poor people who are capable of are not a good idea of them.
The more people who are concerned about Israel is not a good idea of Israel.